brivity.com 2019-03-31

# Brivity's Privacy Policy – Brivity Help

**Privacy Policy**

(last updated 1/16/2019)

**You are entering a binding contract with Brivity, Inc. (Brivity).**  Throughout the site, the terms “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Brivity, Inc.  Brivity, Inc. offers this website, including all information, tools and services available from this Site (collectively, “Services”), to you, the user, conditioned upon your acceptance of all terms, conditions, policies and notices stated herein.  Any new features or tools which are added to the Site shall also be subject to this Privacy Policy and Brivity’s Terms of Service.  

By visiting the Site and/or purchasing our Services, you agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy and Brivity’s Terms of Service, which apply to all users of the Site, including without limitation users who are borrowers, vendors, clients, merchants, and/or contributors of content.

Please read this Privacy Policy and Brivity’s Terms of Service carefully before accessing or using the Site. By accessing or using any part of the Site, you agree to be bound by this Policy Privacy and Brivity’s Terms of Service. If you do not agree to all the terms and conditions of this agreement, then you may not access the Site or use any Services. If this Privacy Policy is an offer, acceptance is expressly limited to this Privacy Policy and Brivity’s Terms of Service.

**Your privacy is critically important to us. At Brivity we have a few fundamental principles**

  1. You own your data
  2. We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it
  3. We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights
  4. We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services
  5. We will not sell your information to any 3rd party at any time for any reason

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Personally-Identifying Information is any information that that identifies you or would enable someone to contact you.   **We collect Personally-Identifying Information when you register to use our Services (see Terms of Service), ask a question, conduct a transaction, or send us an email.  If you do not provide the requested information, you may not be able to access or use some or all of our Services.**  

Like most website operators, Brivity collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request.  Brivity’s purpose for collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Brivity’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Brivity may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  

Brivity routinely collects certain types of Personally-Identifying Information, like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, to identify its visitors, however, we do not disclose such information, other than under the circumstances described in this policy.

Certain visitors to Brivity’s websites choose to interact with Brivity in ways that require Brivity to gather Personally-Identifying Information.  The amount and type of information that Brivity gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Brivity by purchasing services from Brivity, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions.  In each case, Brivity collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Brivity. Brivity does not disclose Personally-Identifying Information other than as described in this policy. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities or services.  

**Protection of Personally-Identifying Information**

Brivity uses physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your Personally-Identifying Information.  We use commercially reasonable efforts to protect against malware, viruses, and spyware on our site or as part of the Service.  By using Brivity’s websites or Services you agree to release Brivity from any liability associated with any technical issues caused by the Service, including any malware, viruses, or spyware communicated to your computer or mobile device through any use of the Service. 

Wherever we collect sensitive financial information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way

Brivity takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access to its email lists

**Disclosure of Personally-Identifying Information**

Brivity will not rent or sell Personally-Identifying Information to anyone.  

Brivity discloses Personally-Identifying Information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that: (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Brivity’s behalf or to provide services available at Brivity’s websites, and (ii) that have contractually agreed not to disclose it to others.  Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Brivity’s websites or Services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Brivity discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Brivity believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or security of Brivity, third parties, or the public at large.  

We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics do not include Personally-Identifying Information. 

As Brivity continues to grow, we may buy or sell businesses or assets.  If all or substantially all of Brivity’s business or assets are acquired by a third party, our users’ Personally-Identifying Information will generally be one of the transferred business assets.  We reserve the right to include your Personally-Identifying Information, collected as an asset, in any such transfer to a third party.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns.  Brivity uses cookies to help Brivity identify and track visitors, their usage of Brivity website, and their website access preferences. Brivity visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Brivity’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Brivity’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

**External Links.**   Our websites may have links to other companies or organizations.  We are not responsible for how these other companies or organizations collect, use, disclose, or secure the information that you provide them. If you choose to access a third-party website through a link provided as part of our Service, you do so at your own risk and subject to any terms of service or privacy policy (if any) associated with such third-party website.  Similarly, we use third party-provided APIs and other tools to receive information from accounts to which you give us access (e.g., your email account(s) and your CRM platform). We are not responsible for errors or other issues associated with the functionality of such APIs and other tools.

**Collection of Information from Minors.** Brivity does not direct our Service specifically to minors.  We do not knowingly collect or use minors’ Personally-Identifying Information.  If we learn that a user is a minor, we will promptly delete any Personally-Identifying Information we have collected about that user. If you are a minor, please do not send us any information about yourself.

**Consent to Processing in the United States.**  By providing Brivity with any Personally-Identifying Information and/or Content, all users, including, without limitation, users in Canada, Mexico, and Europe, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the transfer of such Personally-Identifying Information across international borders in accordance with Brivity’s standard operations, including the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America or other countries in which our employees and contractors may be located.

**TELEPHONE CONSUMER PROTECTION ACT (TCPA) FOR UNITED STATES RESIDENTS**

If you are a United States resident using our website and services, you represent and warrant that:

  1. you are at least 18 years old;
  2. you live in the United States;
  3. you are the account holder for the email addresses and phone numbers you provided, or you have authorization from the account holder to give this consent; and
  4. the email addresses and phone numbers you provide are accurate, and you will let us know if you release them to another

**Mobile Service.** Please note that our mobile service is available only in certain states. Certain mobile features may be incompatible with your carrier or mobile device.  Contact your carrier with questions regarding these issues.

  *****PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING PARAGRAPHS CAREFULLY.  DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE OR REGISTER FOR SERVICES IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO COMPLY*****

**EXPRESS WRITTEN CONSENT.** BY SUBMITTING YOUR CONTACT INFORMATION, YOU ARE PROVIDING YOUR EXPRESS WRITTEN CONSENT TO RECEIVE COMMUNICATIONS FROM US AT ANY EMAIL ADDRESS OR TELEPHONE NUMBER THAT YOU PROVIDE TO US, EVEN IF YOU ARE REGISTERED ON A NATIONAL OR STATE DO-NOT-CALL LIST. YOUR CONSENT HERE ALSO SERVES AS YOUR EXPRESS WRITTEN CONSENT TO YOUR PAST RECEIPT OF ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS FROM US. 

E-MAILS, CALLS, AND TEXTS. THESE COMMUNICATIONS MAY INCLUDE TELEMARKETING MESSAGES, THROUGH THE USE OF EMAIL, LANDLINE PHONE, FAX, CELLULAR PHONE, AND TEXT MESSAGES (INCLUDING SMS AND MMS).

**AUTODIALING.** WE MAY USE AN AUTOMATIC TELEPHONE DIALING SYSTEM (OR “AUTO-DIALER”), WHICH MAY EMPLOY AN ARTIFICIAL OR PRE-RECORDED VOICE OR “ROBOTEXTS.” YOUR CARRIER’S STANDARD RATES AND CHARGES MAY APPLY.

**NO PURCHASE NECESSARY.** AGREEING TO THESE COMMUNICATIONS IS NOT A CONDITION OF PURCHASING ANY PROPERTY, GOODS, OR SERVICES FROM US.   

**OPTING OUT.** YOU MAY REVOKE YOUR CONSENT TO RECEIVE COMMUNICATIONS AT ANY TIME BY REPLYING “STOP” TO ANY OF OUR TEXTS, OR BY ANY OTHER REASONABLE MEANS. WE WILL MAKE A COMMERCIALLY REASONABLE EFFORT TO COMPLY WITH ANY COMMUNICATIONS FROM YOU OPTING OUT, BUT REPLY “STOP” WILL AUTOMATICALLY UNSUBSCRIBE YOU, AND WE RECOMMEND THAT METHOD. WE MAY TAKE UP TO 30 DAYS TO STOP COMMUNICATIONS IF YOU USE A METHOD OTHER THAN THE AUTOMATIC REPLY “STOP.” YOU CONSENT TO RECEIVE A FINAL TEXT MESSAGE CONFIRMING YOUR OPT-OUT.

**COMMUNICATION FREQUENCY.** HOW OFTEN WE SEND YOU COMMUNICATIONS WILL VARY BECAUSE THE INDIVIDUAL SALESPERSON OR REALTOR WHO COMMUNICATES WITH YOU WILL DETERMINE IT.

**Change & Discontinuance.**  Brivity reserves the right to update, change or replace any part of this Privacy Policy by posting updates and/or changes to its websites. Your continued use of the Services after the effectiveness of such changes will constitute acceptance of and agreement to any such changes. You further waive any right you may have to receive specific notice of minor changes to this Privacy Policy.  

**Notice of Changes.  **Any material revision to Brivity’s Privacy Policy will be communicated to users by means of an email notice prior to the change taking effect.  Users are encouraged to periodically review Brivity’s Privacy Policy for the latest privacy statement information.

**Questions.** If you have any question about Brivity’s Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at [support@brivity.com](mailto:support@brivity.com) or mail us at Brivity, c/o Legal Compliance Department, 2211 Rimland Drive STE 124, Bellingham, WA 98226.

**Your California Privacy Rights** **.**  As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share Personally-Identifying Information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless we clearly identify the third party and you affirmatively agree to such disclosure.  If you do not want your Personally-Identifying Information shared third parties for the purpose of direct marketing, do not opt in to such use. If you do ask us to share your information with a third party for its marketing purposes, we will only share information in connection with that specific activity, as we do not share information with any third party on a continual basis.

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by emailing [support@brivity.com](mailto:support@brivity.com) or by mail at Brivity, c/o Legal Compliance Department, 2211 Rimland Drive STE 124, Bellingham, WA 98226.

**GOOGLE INTEGRATION.   **A lead within Brivity represents a person or entity with whom you have an established or potential business relationship.  Contacts within Brivity include leads, clients, vendors, and collaborators.   **By connecting your Google Gmail account to Brivity, you are granting Brivity express permission to (on your behalf), access, send, receive, and store emails from certain contacts in your now integrated Gmail account.**   Furthermore, once connected, all future email activity managed via your Brivity account will utilize your integrated Gmail account. Please note that Brivity stores only those email messages that are sent, received, or carbon copied to contacts located within your Brivity account, and all such emails will be viewable by persons who have access to your Brivity account.  Emails stored in the Brivity data base are protected by two layers of industry-standard encryption.
